SIDDHI GHADIGAONKAR

HUMAN RESOURCES



PERSONAL PROFILE

Attentive and communicative human resources manager with ten years of experience. Strong written and verbal communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to gain trust combine to achieve results. Experienced in managing personnel records management, compensation and benefits, and employee relations. Proven track record of crafting effective training and development tools

SKILLS

01. COMMUNICATION

02. LEADERSHIP

03. TIME MANAGEMENT

04.DECISION MAKING

05.HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT

06. EMPLOYEE RELATIONS

07. RECRUITMENT

08. ORGANIZATION SKILLS

WORK EXPERIENCE

June2022 -till

HR Manager

Cyquent India PVT LTD.

- since it's a US-based company, I am responsible for US IT Non-IT recruitment (B2B, Direct) as well as India location as well.
- managing Joining Formalities i.e Documents collection, and preparing Offer Letters for candidates.
- Coordinating with the administration department as per requirement.
- I always ready to learn new skills which can help to work better as HR.

Aug2021 - Feb2022 (Contract)

Link Group

HR SR.IT Recruiter

- Responsibilities include identifying future hiring needs, designing job descriptions, sourcing candidates through databases and social media, conducting interviews, and filing paperwork.
- Screening those who applied carefully on skill sets that will best fit into the company culture and budget.

Nov 2020- Aug 2021

Deputy Manager HR

Finetec Glazing Systems LLP

- Set up all Human Resources Policies and Rules in the HQ and Factory $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$
- Make proper organisation chart and further each position JD / KRA $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$
- Follow up and coordinate with Sales and factory team for better results $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$
- Entire recruitment process and after joining formalities, induction programme at HQ Employee engagement activity i.e. Vishwakarma Pooja, Diwali,etc.
- Guest Arrangement i.e. lunch / vehicle arrangements etc. if required-
- Employee counselling and Brainstorming-
- Leave and daily attendance management through Bio Matric system •
- Flight and other booking administrations if any -
- Coordinate with factory employee on daily basis •
- Coordinate with sales team for monthly sales $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$
- Employment Verification & Background Check •
- Releasing Offer and appointment Letters
- Employee life cycle Joining to Exit (including maintaining personal file) Other administrative day to day task etc.•
- Review new join HQ employee performance on three monthly basis and update management accordingly, ensure PMS system

Apr 2018 - Nov 2020

Assistant Manager HR

Hunger INC Hospitality PVT LTD

- Entire Recruitment Cycle: Checking for the Budget, pre-joining documentation, current CTC of the candidate with the proposed CTC, and getting the required approvals before issuing the offers.
- Onboarding & Induction: New employees onboarding and exit employees exit formalities
- Performance Appraisals: Issuing Offer Letters, Appointment Letters, Transfer Letters & Confirmation Letters. To provide written notification to all staff of any changes in pay.
- Training & Development: Implementing and explaining HR policies
- Attendance & Leave Management: To ensure manual and computerized records are accurately maintained and updated regularly in line with data protection. Monthly updating of the Leave records of all the Employees & following up on the Leave applications with the Employees.
- Payroll & Statutory Compliance: To arrange the payment of staff salaries through the computerized payroll system. This will involve the collation and input of all relevant information for the monthly payroll (including new starters, leavers, benefits, contract changes, sickness absence payments, and maternity and paternity pay). To provide advice to staff and managers in relation to pay, salary guidelines, taxation, and National Insurance.
- Employee Engagement: Planning parties for employees. Celebration of festivals, birthdays, and successes. Arrange internal parties for employees and external parties with clients. • Participating and Discussing with Management regarding the new policies, coordinate with other location Managers

Aug 2015 - Mar 2018

Sr. Executive-Administration HR

- Phonographic Performance LTD To provide written notification to all staff of any changes in pay.
 - To provide advice to staff and managers in relation to pay, salary guidelines, taxation, and National Insurance.
 - Query and grievances handling of the Employees. •
 - Taking Exit-Interview and Issuing Reliving letters & full and final statements of existing employees.
 - Participating and Discussing with Management regarding the new policies.
 - · Maintaining the records of the employee by maintaining their personal file.
 - Handling recruitment through various streams like Naukri, Monster, Etc.
 - Organize small events/ festival Celebrations for employees.(Food, Decoration) / adequacy of Sub Staff) Courier & Dispatch (Inward / Outward / Outstation) / also making a record of Local maintenance.
 - · Keeping details of all petty cash expenses with proper approvals from the Director, forwarding details of all expenses to the Accounts team.
 - · Coordination and maintenance of systems related to Housekeeping.
 - Managing vendors and keeping track of the cycle of all maintenance contracts and AMCs... · Coordinating with Travel Agencies for Airlines & Railway bookings, Hotel bookings & Car arrangements for employees & guests. Finalise vendors and do negotiations toward price, payments, and quality

Aug 2009 - Dec 2014

Executive-Administration HR

SES Technologies LTD.

- · Query and grievances handling of the Employees.
- Taking Exit-Interview and Issuing Reliving letters & full and final statements of existing employees.
- Participating and Discussing with Management regarding the new policies.
- Maintaining the records of the employee by maintaining their personal file.
- · Handling recruitment through various streams like Naukri, Monster, Etc.
- Organize small events/ festival Celebrations for employees.(Food, Decoration) / adequacy of Sub Staff) Courier & Dispatch (Inward / Outward / Outstation) / also making a record of Local maintenance.
- Keeping details of all petty cash expenses with proper approvals from the Director, forwarding details of all expenses to the Accounts team.
- Coordination and maintenance of systems related to Housekeeping.
- Managing vendors and keeping track of the cycle of all maintenance contracts and AMCs.
- Coordinating with Travel Agencies for Airlines & Railway bookings, Hotel bookings & Car arrangements for employees & guests. Finalise vendors and do negotiations toward price, payments, and quality

Mar 2006 - Jun 2009

Front Office Asst. cum Reservation Executive

Fariyas Hotel PVT

- · Handled all the duties of this position like welcoming and greeting guests.Responsible for receiving incoming calls and attending to callers' requests in a professional manner.
- · Responsible for handling queries of guests and customers.
- Assist to Travel desk.
- Taking care of couriers and maintaining office stationery for the front office department.
- · Managing and training the Front Office staff
- · Ensuring the front desk provides a professional and friendly service for guests
- Arranging staff scheduling.
- Acting as a liaison between General Manager and staff •
- · Handled checkouts for rooms (preparing the bills and taking payments)
- Handling foreign exchange.
- · Co-ordinate with the food and beverage department while conducting functions and seminar

Mazgaon Dock LTD. An ARTIST(Painter) (part of diploma)- 01 YEAR

EDUCATION

- Passed MBA (HR) in 2014 from Ulyanovsk State University(Russian Federation)
- Passed Diploma (3yrs)-Painting in 2005 from Mumbai Board
- Passed H.S.C in 2003 from Mumbai Board.
- Passed S.S.C in 2001 from Mumbai Board.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Won 'Best Employee of the Month-Sept'06 in Fariyas Hotel.
- Stage Performer as a Singer
- Active member of SARRP'-Spreading Awareness On Reptiles & Rehabilitation Programme.
- Active Vadak of Tradition Dhol Tasha Pathak of Mumbai. le Samna Dhol Tasha
 & Dhwaj Pathak

TECHNICAL

- Ms Office
- DTP (Graphics).
- Tally ERP 9

STRENGHTS

- Enthusiastic to learn new things.
- Positive attitude.
- Flexibility.

LANGUAGE KNOWN

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

CONTACT

PHONE NUMBER

+91 91673 44204

DOB

20 APRIL 1986

E-MAIL ADDRESS

SID20085@GMAIL.COM

CURRENT ADDRESS

PERMANENT ADDRESS

PUNE

MUMBAI